Finding aid to the Classes of 1901-1910 records CA.MS.01020
Smith College Archives
- Class of 1905 Records, 1901-1975; 14.458 linear feet (17 containers)
  - Senior Dramatics- A.C. Bradley, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics- Groups, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics- E.T. Babcock, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics- M. Lockwood, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics- K. C. Noyles, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 7)
  - Senior Dramatics- Costume Book, 1905 (Box 1678, Folder 8)
  - Costume, Memorabilia, 1955 (Box 1680)
  - Class Secretary's Card File (Box 1680)
  - Pillowcases and Banner (Box 1680)
  - Individuals A-El (Box 1673)
  - Individuals Em-P (Box 1675)
  - Individuals Q-Z (Box 1677)
  - Burnham, Ella Kellogg (class notes, memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1674)
  - Emerson, Ella May (memorabilia book and photo album) (Box 1681)
  - Hamilton, Irene (memorabilia book) (Box 1676)
  - Lawlor, Alice Teresa (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1682)
  - Perry, Marjorie (class file, photograph albums) (Box 1682.1)
  - Pond, Jean Baird (memorabilia book) (Box 1683)
  - Webster, Laura Josephine (photo albums) (Box 1679)
  - Will, Edith Charlotte (photo albums) (Box 1679)
  - Wright, Helen (photo album) (Box 1679)
  - Sister Mary Francis Louise (Maryknoll Sisters: A Pictorial History) (Box 1683.1)
- Class of 1906 Records, 1902-1971; 9.875 linear feet (21 containers)
  The Class of 1906 was the twenty-eighth entering class and the twenty-eighth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1906 records, 1902-1971, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1906, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, financial information, minutes, and other memorabilia.
  - Alumnae Fund List, 1956-1964 (Box 1684, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate, 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 2)
  - Sophomore Basketball Team, 1904 (Box 1684, Folder 3)
  - Class Letters, 1926-1963 (Box 1684, Folder 4)
  - Fund Letters, 1923-1966 (Box 1684, Folder 5)
  - Groups, 1902-1906 (Box 1684, Folder 6)
  - Regional Lists, 1968-1969 (Box 1684, Folder 7)
  - Scholarships and Bequests, 1960-1969 (Box 1684, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Notebook, 1902-1921 (Box 1684, Folder 9)
  - Smith College Relief Unit, 1918 (Box 1684, Folder 10)
  - Class Supper, 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 11)
  - Commencement, 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Music, 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 14)
  - Freshman Grind by 1905, 1902 (Box 1684, Folder 15)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1902-1903 (Box 1684, Folder 16)
  - Granddaughter's Scarf, Clubs, 1941; undated (Box 1684, Folder 17)
  - History, undated (Box 1684, Folder 18)
  - Ivy Day, 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 19)
  - Ivy Day Photos, 1906 (Box 1684, Folder 20)
  - Junior Frolic, 1905 (Box 1684, Folder 21)
  - Junior Prom, 1905 (Box 1684, Folder 22)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1961-1969 (Box 1684.1, Folder 1)
  - Necrology, undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 2)
  - Officers, undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 3)
  - Organization, undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 4)
  - President's Notebook, 1906-1956 (Box 1684.1, Folder 5)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1684.1, Folder 6)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1902 (Box 1684.1, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Records, 1902-1943 (Box 1684.1, Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1906-1961 (Box 1684.1, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1685, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1907 (Box 1685, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1909 (Box 1685, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1911 (Box 1685, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1916 (Box 1685, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1921 (Box 1685, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1925 (Box 1685, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1929 (Box 1685, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1931 (Box 1685, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1931 (Box 1685, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 1685, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1936 (Box 1685, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 1685, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1941 (Box 1685, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1946 (Box 1685.1, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1951 (Box 1685.1, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1956 (Box 1685.1, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1961 (Box 1685.1, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1966 (Box 1685.1, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1971 (Box 1685.1, Folder 6)
  - Reunions- General, undated (Box 1685.1, Folder 7)
  - Reunions- Songs, undated (Box 1685.1, Folder 8)
  - Reunion Materials, undated (Box 1685.1, Folder 9)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 4)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 5)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1906 (Box 1686, Folder 6)
  - Senior Dramatics- Smith College Club of New York, 1907 (Box 1686, Folder 7)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1907 (Box 1686, Folder 8)
  - Banner and Memorabilia (Box 1684.2)
  - Individuals A-Ba (Box 1687)
  - Individuals Be-G (Box 1688)
  - Individuals H-L (Box 1688.1)
  - Individuals Ma-Mi (Box 1689)
  - Individuals Mo-Se (Box 1690)
  - Individuals Sh-Z (Box 1691)
  - Bacon, Caroline A. Wood (photo album) (Box 1691.1)
  - Bartlett, Sarah Ripley (memorabilia book, photo album) (Box 1692)
  - Dearborn, Bernice Walker (memorabilia book) (Box 1693)
  - Kauffmann, Barbara (memorabilia book) (Box 1698)
  - Marble, Anna Theresa (memorabilia book) (Box 1699)
  - Mason, Janet de Witt (photo album) (Box 1700)
  - Norton, Margaret (memorabilia book) (Box 1700)
  - Scharps, Hannah de Rothschild (memorabilia book) (Box 1701)
  - Scharps, Hannah de Rothschild (correspondence, diary, class work) (Box 1702)
  - Streeter, Mary Adelaide Roxana (memorabilia book) (Box 1702.1)
- Class of 1907 Records, 1902-1977; 14.0 linear feet (23 containers)
  The Class of 1907 was the twenty-ninth entering class and the twenty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1907 records, 1902-1977, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1907, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
  - Animal, undated (Box 1703, Folder 1)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Music, 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Photos, 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 5)
  - Group Photos, 1902-1907 (Box 1703, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1903 (Box 1703, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Grind given by 1906, 1903 (Box 1703, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Frolic given by 1906, 1903 (Box 1703, Folder 9)
  - History, undated (Box 1703, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day Photos, 1907 (Box 1703, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom, 1906 (Box 1703, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom Picnic, 1906 (Box 1703, Folder 14)
  - Junior Ushers, 1906 (Box 1703, Folder 15)
  - Class Letters, 1917-1976 (Box 1703, Folder 16)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 2)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 3)
  - Senior Dramatics- Costume Design, 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 4)
  - Prize Song, undated (Box 1704, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1908 (Box 1704, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1910 (Box 1704, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1912 (Box 1704, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1917 (Box 1704, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1927 (Box 1704, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1932 (Box 1704, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1937 (Box 1704, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1942 (Box 1704, Folder 13)
  - Reunions, 1947 (Box 1704, Folder 14)
  - Reunions, 1952 (Box 1704, Folder 15)
  - Reunions, 1957 (Box 1704, Folder 16)
  - Reunions, 1962 (Box 1704, Folder 17)
  - Reunions, 1967 (Box 1704, Folder 18)
  - Reunions, 1972 (Box 1704, Folder 19)
  - Reunions, 1977 (Box 1704, Folder 20)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1704, Folder 21)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1904 (Box 1704, Folder 22)
  - Class Seal, 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 23)
  - Class Supper, 1907 (Box 1704, Folder 24)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: A-B, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 1)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: C, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 2)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: D-F, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 3)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: G-H, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 4)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: J-L, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 5)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: M-N, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 6)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: O-P, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 7)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: R, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 8)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: S, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 9)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: T-V, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 10)
  - 25th Reunion Questionnaires: W-Z, 1932 (Box 1705, Folder 11)
  - 30th Reunion Questionnaires: A-C, 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 12)
  - 30th Reunion Questionnaires: D-H, 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 13)
  - 30th Reunion Questionnaires: J-N, 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 14)
  - 30th Reunion Questionnaires: O-S, 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 15)
  - 30th Reunion Questionnaires: T-Z, 1937 (Box 1705, Folder 16)
  - Class Secretary's Book, 1903-1937 (Box 1706, Folder 1)
  - Register of the Class of 1907, 1908-1962 (Box 1706, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary's Records, 1907-1963 (Box 1706, Folder 3)
  - Class Secretary's Records, 1907-1963 (Box 1706, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1928-1961 (Box 1706, Folder 5)
  - Class Secretary's scrapbooks (Box 1706.1)
  - Class secretary's scrapbooks (Box 1715.5)
  - Individuals A-F (Box 1707)
  - Individuals G-H (Box 1707.1)
  - Individuals I-O (Box 1708)
  - Individuals P-Sc (Box 1709)
  - Individuals Se-Z (Box 1710)
  - Bradbury, Pearle Lord (scrapbook) (Box 1712.2)
  - Brodrick, Isabel (photo album) (Box 1712.1)
  - Churchill, Anna Quincy (memorabilia book) (Box 1715.4)
  - Daniels, Elinor Lothorp (memorabilia book) (Box 1715.1)
  - Dow, Ethel Robinson (memorabilia book) (Box 1711)
  - Dow, Ethel Robinson (photo album) (Box 1715.3)
  - Felt, Marion (memorabilia book) (Box 1712)
  - Goodman, Alice Edith (photo album) (Box 1715.3)
  - Hale, Mary Kimball (album) (Box 1715.6)
  - Hilliard, Carrie Gertrude (memorabilia book) (Box 1712)
  - Jackson, Florence (scrapbook) (Box 1712.2)
  - Little, Eleanor Johnson (memorabilia book) (Box 1712.1)
  - Noyes, Mary (memorabilia book) (Box 1713)
  - Noyes, Mary (line-a-day book, photo albums) (Box 1715.4)
  - Pitman, Margareth Arnold (memorabilia book) (Box 1715.3)
  - Richmond, Myrtle Leila (memorabilia book) (Box 1713.1)
  - Senior, Clara (memorabilia book) (Box 1715.2)
  - Sherman, Hope (class note, memorabilia book) (Box 1714)
  - Tolman, Olive (memorabilia book) (Box 1715)
- Class of 1908 Records, 1904-1978; 16.208 linear feet (25 containers)
  The Class of 1908 was the thirtieth entering class and the thirtieth graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1908 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1908, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 2)
  - Commencement- Music, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 3)
  - Commencement- Photographs, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Grind by 1907, 1904 (Box 1732, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1904-1903 (Box 1732, Folder 7)
  - Gifts- Bells, 1955 (Box 1732, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1904-1908 (Box 1732, Folder 9)
  - Ivy Day, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day- Photographs, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 11)
  - Junior Prom, 1907 (Box 1732, Folder 12)
  - Junior Prom- Garden Party, 1907 (Box 1732, Folder 13)
  - Junior Ushers, 1907 (Box 1732, Folder 14)
  - Class Letters, 1954-1975 (Box 1732, Folder 15)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 16)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 17)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 18)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1732, Folder 19)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1905 (Box 1732, Folder 20)
  - Class Supper, 1908 (Box 1732, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer's Records- Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 1732, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer's Records- Ledger Book, 1928-1973 (Box 1732, Folder 23)
  - Necrology, 1959-1971 (Box 1732, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1909-1918 (Box 1733, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1923-1928 (Box 1733, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1933-1938 (Box 1733, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1948-1958 (Box 1733, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1963 (Box 1733, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1968 (Box 1733, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1978 (Box 1733, Folder 7)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files (Box 1733.1)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files- Graduates (Box 1733.2)
  - Class Secretary's Card Files- Children, Non-Graduates (Box 1633.3)
  - Class Secretary's Scrapbooks, reunion memorabilia, Senior Dramatics Album (missing)
  - Individuals A-D (Box 1734)
  - Individuals E-F (Box 1735)
  - Individuals G-O (Box 1736)
  - Individuals P-Sj (Box 1737)
  - Individuals Sm-Sw (Box 1738)
  - Individuals T-Z (Box 1739)
  - Appleton, Helen (photo album) (Box 1744.1)
  - Bosart, Dora Ellen (memorabilia book) (Box 1744.2)
  - Bosart, Dora Ellen (memorabilia book) (Box 1744.3)
  - Burton, Flora Emma (1955 album of tributes) (Box 1744.4)
  - Ellsworth, Helen Clare (photograph album and memorabilia album) (Box 1740)
  - Gallagher, Edith Charters (scrapbook) (Box 1740.1)
  - Moore, Gretchen (photo albums, zoology lab notebooks) (Box 1744.5)
  - Morgan, Nannie Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1744.6)
  - Morgan, Nannie Louise (memorabilia book) (Box 1744.7)
  - Smith, Mary Byers (photographs, photo album) (Box 1744.8)
  - Stahl, Alice Emeline (photo album) (Box 1744.8)
  - Stoddard, Florence Huldah (memorabilia book) (Box 1741)
  - Sumner, Amie May Rand (memorabilia book) (Box 1742)
  - Whitcomb, Helen May (memorabilia book) (Box 1743)
  - Wight, Gwendolen Ross (memorabilia book) (Box 1744)
  - Unidentified scrapbooks (Box 1744.9)
- Class of 1909 Records, 1905-1975; 12.25 linear feet (23 containers)
  The Class of 1909 was the thirty-first entering class and the thirty-first graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1909 records, 1905-1975, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1909, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, Class Secretary's records, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 2)
  - Commencement-Music, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 3)
  - Commencement-Photographs, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Speaker, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Frolic, 1905 (Box 1745, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind, 1905 (Box 1745, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1905-1906 (Box 1745, Folder 8)
  - Freshman Reception, 1905 (Box 1745, Folder 9)
  - Groups, 1905-1909 (Box 1745, Folder 10)
  - Ivy Day, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day-Photographs, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 12)
  - Junior Frolic, 1908 (Box 1745, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1908 (Box 1745, Folder 14)
  - Junior Prom-Garden Party, 1908 (Box 1745, Folder 15)
  - Junior Ushers, 1908 (Box 1745, Folder 16)
  - Class Letters, 1922-1975 (Box 1745, Folder 17)
  - Memorabilia, undated (Box 1745, Folder 18)
  - Last Sing, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 19)
  - Class Secretary's Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 1745, Folder 20)
  - Class Supper, 1909 (Box 1745, Folder 21)
  - Alumnae Quarterly Clippings, 1944-1951 (Box 1745, Folder 22)
  - Alumnae Quarterly Clippings, 1952-1973 (Box 1745, Folder 23)
  - Reunions, 1910 (Box 1745, Folder 24)
  - Reunions, 1912 (Box 1745, Folder 25)
  - Reunions, 1914 (Box 1745, Folder 26)
  - Reunions, 1919 (Box 1745, Folder 27)
  - Reunions, 1924 (Box 1745, Folder 28)
  - Reunion Book, 1924 (Box 1745, Folder 29)
  - Reunions, 1929 (Box 1745, Folder 30)
  - Reunions, 1934 (Box 1745, Folder 31)
  - Reunions, 1939 (Box 1746, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1944 (Box 1746, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1949 (Box 1746, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1954 (Box 1746, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1959 (Box 1746, Folder 5)
  - Reunions, 1964 (Box 1746, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box 1746, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1974 (Box 1746, Folder 8)
  - Class Secretary's Records-A-B (Box 1746, Folder 9)
  - Class Secretary's Records-C-D (Box 1746, Folder 10)
  - Class Secretary's Records-E-G (Box 1746, Folder 11)
  - Class Secretary's Records-H-J (Box 1746, Folder 12)
  - Class Secretary's Records-K-L (Box 1746, Folder 13)
  - Class Secretary's Records-M (Box 1746, Folder 14)
  - Class Secretary's Records-N-R (Box 1746, Folder 15)
  - Class Secretary's Records-S (Box 1746, Folder 16)
  - Class Secretary's Records-T-W (Box 1746, Folder 17)
  - Class Secretary's Notes II-K-R (Box 1746, Folder 18)
  - Class Secretary's Notes II-S-Z (Box 1746, Folder 19)
  - Non-Graduates: Class Secretary's Notes (Box 1746, Folder 20)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1909 (Box 1747)
    - Senior Dramatics: Business Manager's Report, 1909 (Box 1747)
    - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1909 (Box 1747)
    - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1909 (Box 1747)
    - Senior Dramatics: Photographs, 1909 (Box 1747)
  - Senior Reception, 1909 (Box 1747)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1747)
  - Banner (Box 1747.1)
  - Individuals A-F (Box 1748)
  - Individuals G-H (Box 1748.1)
  - Individuals J-Ri (Box 1749)
  - Individuals Ro-T (Box 1749.1)
  - Individuals U-Z (Box 1750)
  - Andrews, Helen Rhoda (photo album) (Box 1751)
  - Blair, Margaret Amidon (ex-1909), 1905-1907 (Box 1751.1)
  - Byers, Harriet Gertrude (photo album) (Box 1757.4)
  - Chapman, Elizabeth (Scrapbook) (Box 1748.2)
  - Dana, Helen (memorabilia book) (Box 1751)
  - Dempsey, Leah Boylan (memorabilia book) (Box 1752)
  - Dempsey, Leah Boylan (memorabilia book) (Box 1753)
  - Dodge, Margaret Nutter (photograph album) (Box 1757.6)
  - Harris, Helen Osborne (photo album) (Box 1757.5)
  - Hatfield, Margaret (memorabilia book) (Box 1754)
  - Hatfield, Margaret (memorabilia book) (Box 1755)
  - Henley, Ruth (photograph album) (Box 1757.6)
  - Holland, Sue Warren (photo album) (Box 1757.5)
  - Homer, Dora (photograph album) (Box 1757.6)
  - Homer, Dora (photograph album) (Box 1757.3)
  - Parsons, Pearl Frances (memorabilia book) (Box 1756)
  - Pierce, Alice Marjorie (photo album) (Box 1757.5)
  - Swift, Lucy Esther (photo album) (Box 1757.5)
  - Thornburg, Myra Haldeman (photo albums) (Box 1757.4)
  - Upton, Eleanor Stuart (memorabilia book and English notebooks) (Box 1757)
  - Upton, Eleanor Stuart (correspondence) (Box 1757.1)
  - Upton, Eleanor Stuart (lecture notes) (Box 1757.2)
- Class of 1910 Records, 1906-1984; 16.979 linear feet (27 containers)
  The Class of 1910 was the thirty-second entering class and the thirty-second graduating class of Smith College.
  The Class of 1910 records, 1906-1984, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1910, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, treasury information, and other memorabilia.
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 1)
  - Class Letters, 1919-1984 (Box 1758, Folder 2)
  - Class Secretary, 1906-1980 (Box 1758, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Music, 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Photographs, 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Grind by 1909, 1906 (Box 1758, Folder 7)
  - Freshman Handbook, 1906-1907 (Box 1758, Folder 8)
  - Groups, 1906-1910 (Box 1758, Folder 9)
  - Group; Bacon Bat, 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 10)
  - History, 1906-1910 (Box 1758, Folder 11)
  - Ivy Day, 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 12)
  - Ivy Day Photographs, 1910 (Box 1758, Folder 13)
  - Junior Prom, 1909 (Box 1758, Folder 14)
  - Junior Ushers, 1909 (Box 1758, Folder 15)
  - Senior Dramatics, 1910 (Box 1759, Folder 1)
  - Senior Dramatics- Photographs, 1910 (Box 1759, Folder 2)
  - Songs, undated (Box 1759, Folder 3)
  - Class Supper, 1910 (Box 1759, Folder 4)
  - Sophomore Reception, 1908 (Box 1759, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Records- Ledger Book, 1906-1970 (Box 1759, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Records- Ledger Book, 1916-1970 (Box 1759, Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's Records- Reports, 1935-1966 (Box 1759, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, undated (Box 1760, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1911 (Box 1760, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1915 (Box 1760, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1920 (Box 1760, Folder 4)
  - Reunions, 1920 (Box 1760, Folder 5)
  - Reunions: Questionnaire, 1920 (Box 1760, Folder 6)
  - Reunions, 1925 (Box 1760, Folder 7)
  - Reunions, 1930 (Box 1761, Folder 1)
  - Reunions, 1935 (Box 1761, Folder 2)
  - Reunions, 1940-1950 (Box 1761, Folder 3)
  - Reunions, 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 4)
  - Reunions: Questionnaires A-C, 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 5)
  - Reunions: Questionnaires D-L, 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 6)
  - Reunions: Questionnaires M-R, 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 7)
  - Reunions: Questionnaires S-Z, 1955 (Box 1761, Folder 8)
  - Reunions, 1960 (Box 1761, Folder 9)
  - Reunions, 1965 (Box 1761, Folder 10)
  - Reunions, 1970 (Box 1761, Folder 11)
  - Reunions, 1975 (Box 1761, Folder 12)
  - Reunions, 1980 (Box 1761, Folder 13)
  - Reunion Songs, undated (Box 1761, Folder 14)
  - Banner (Box 1761.1)
  - Individuals A-C (Box 1762)
  - Individuals D-Man (Box 1763)
  - Individuals Mar-Sp (Box 1764)
  - Individuals St-Z (Box 1765)
  - Baldwin, Sidney (diary, memorabilia and photograph album) (Box 1767)
  - Barry, Gertrude Martha (diary, memorabilia book) (Box 1766)
  - Bradley, Helen Osgood (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.1)
  - Fuller, Edna May (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.2)
  - Jenison, Eva (memorabilia book and photograph album) (Box 1768)
  - Jones, Helen Swift (Box 1768.1)
  - Kilborne, Mary Allerton (photo album) (Box 1770.3)
  - Mansfield, Portia (Ph.D. thesis, New York University) (Box 1770.3)
  - Marden, Louise Ethel (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.4)
  - Metcalf, Winifred Christina (photo album) (Box 1770.5)
  - O'Meara, Alice Stephanie (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.5)
  - Owen, Mildred Van der Velde (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.6)
  - Park, Caroline (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.7)
  - Peterson, Mary (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.8)
  - Ryder, Evelyn Louise (botany and zoology notebooks) (Box 1770.9)
  - Staples, Mary Anne (memorabilia book) (Box 1769)
  - Taylor, Susan Eleanor (diary, album pages) (Box 1770)
  - Valentine, Marjorie (photograph album) (Box 1770.10)
  - Wesby, Maude Earle (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.11)
  - Wilson, Ethel Somers (memorabilia book) (Box 1770.12)